Soon, first of all, the name of the stock has
appeared in front of you.
After 800 minutes of stock trading, we are talking about ACC Limited. So, let's
talk about
today's market for it.
You can see that today's
date is 5.50 PM IST. If we talk about today, then it came out that
your building has seen a
rise of about eight and a half points around zero. You
can also say that the decision has been based on a flat positive or around 1 pulsar
momentum system.
So, till now, let me tell you that you will see these three
levels tomorrow. So,
you all know that the
series of quarterly results has also started. The
results of some big companies have come and the
results of these three companies are going to
come tomorrow as well. So friends,
why am I filling the stop tomorrow? I am going to
tell you that till those days, you must keep an
eye on those days. I am not talking about mixing by trading, I am
just reading.
You can get a full opportunity to print a very good well tomorrow.
Then the
market itself.  But it's not going to make any difference if the
market
saw a decline today.
Sudhir, and
you saw the market this morning. The Inheritance Bank
performed so well because
its results from here to Madras were quite good,
so the results will be good, and even if we
saw a decline in the market, it's very interesting, but
we will do it. Suppose the
market goes up and we don't want to eat, then
you can get a
chance to earn a good amount of money in the ball stock. Let's
talk about all that right now. The
limit from Harold means that it belongs to us. The
name of the chapter is the
cement sector. And a very
powerful point of the semester, it is a very social company. The
universe of the long time, if you want to do it,
you can keep an eye on this topic.
But do not rush into making any investment in the stock tomorrow. I
would like to tell you that look, there was a
discussion going on in the market about the French company,
which may come down a little,
luckily you may see a little weak.
If this really happened, you could
see a decline in the stock.  If you
are an investor, you should
wait for the 950 level in the stock.
I think 930 is a very important support level for this topic.
Before that, you
should look at the 11:00 method. The ribbon of olive oil stock at 1060 does a
very good job of
taking support. So, if you look at your long-term vest, you
can look for a level around 1070 or 950. If you
look at the range of light of the previous record from the first angle, then
you will see tremendous momentum in that time stop and for almost
18 and a half years, it had given indications that you will see a rise.
Look at everything. Even in the short term, this
stock tries to hold on with good volume.
But
if the results are good, then after some time you can
also plan to invest 100 tonnes in this topic.
Apart from that, we will talk directly about
one of our main ones. I will see yesterday's performance to be
a little worse because it has to be done.
All this has also
seen a lot of decline. Now we and approximately  2010 is the day before
yesterday's fall, actually you are seeing,
talk about 500, even now the crop
pattern is visible to some extent and the
interpretation of returns is also around 20%
and if we talk about long-term then
you will get to see a very good long-term chart, as I said, if it is
possible to complete near a major company of cement sector, then
keeping an eye on this problem and talking about the credibility of the people,
you are getting to see a good return of 60%, so out
of three, the
shortage of staff increases towards the second over, then the
name of the second staff has come in front of you
and Stock Kramik Research Limited,
if I am not wrong, then
why did I cover the panel, secondly, both the companies will
reduce my day three, that when you do the last,
you yourself should fill one and only, if
you talk about today's meaning, then from the
marketing dress of print 2020, then it was
almost milk around 1417,
about four rupees stable and on Twitter also
today I saw this and Tapan a flat
lip locking  You have been able to see it for free in the system. As
it is going on in the market, don't be cautious about it. There is a
possibility of it coming closer to the market. So, looking at the pressure on this topic towards tomorrow,
you should
not be arrogant at all. Now, if we talk about this kind of thing, then it looks
quite good for the long term.
So investors are requested to keep an
eye on it. If the result is very
good, then try playing for the first time.
Love triangle, don't even get jealous of your feet.
Friends, if you talk about my Prakash, then
this Stark has also
shown a very good performance in a month. Now,
and
you have seen very good results of about two and a half by a person in a month.
Talk about the
head of a group of stops and then you can see that there is a
decline of around four complexes.
This box is being seen in the interval of one year. We will
compare here the market
decline and here in the decline room, a
big decline in the stock is
not being seen in the year. Apart from this,
you can see the head of the parcel behind the stock, there was a
stop in 5 years.  You will
see a decline and if we talk about approximate returns,
it turns out to be half purchase. I do
n't like half purchases and till now we have talked about the
drama of the staff, as I said, this
best of this turned out to be very good for the long term, so you
can see that the pattern of the stock is
very good for the long term and the pattern will
give top returns, it is a multibagger in the long term,
which came out to be
around 4362 range, so if you are an
inverter and you should still invest, if the
cotton results are good and
you know how to trade, then you will
try to take advantage of it by turning,
even on bad days,
you can take advantage of Anil as well and till now there was a
very good transporter of long-term interest of 212 Shoppers Stop,
after this, sometime
and a very replace psychological level
which is around 140, so even after this, if you want, you
can keep an eye on it, so you will see that
both these stocks look very good,
so you should also keep an eye on them, like the
third stage system, like this, before the big star
moves ahead, definitely like it.
Because your like always increases your fans,
so don't say like, you
must subscribe to the Badshah channel
because Rudra Sharma
tries to guide you by making videos about records,
so do subscribe to the channel. The
village committee head and attractive stock has also come in front of you and we want to tell
you
that if the results are good or
bad tomorrow, do
n't rush into investing in any topper, pay
attention to trading and for short term play,
then let's talk about this trick, today's
restriction comes out to be close around 375,
and we can say that its fans are
quite
Shukradev, approximately
around one and a half dozen,
you can see additional staff in
Chetak, if we talk about the result, then the
positive thing about it is that
its results are expected to be good, that is,
not very good, but the good thing is that this
company can post in this quarter,
if this is really possible, we will
know tomorrow, then a very
good first for you in this talk  You will see this and
one thing that I noticed is that this
topic of life insurance sector of cancer center and
friends are listed in the market that if the
results of this are
good on SBI Life then you will see a rally in both the stops, that is
SBI Life for Marriage Life as well
and my brother-sister
's skin, so if things go bad then we will
see a decline later, so
you will definitely see a negative impact of this on these two stops of SBI Life as well, so
friends, try to keep an eye on this as well,
I would have a
quick look at how the performance of the stock at 1 o'clock looks, so
talk stock here, you
can see the main sources of voice mail behind the talk stop, the
first stop of 1 o'clock comes out quite good
and I have seen about 57 likes, this is a very
good post,
see, in a month many staff have
seen very good results and I have
clearly seen that there has been a big fall in the market, take
advantage of this fall before the market,
in small quantities.
You start investing in good stocks,
but clearly, I know
how many people, after hearing all this, have started
talking about small quantities.
Even now, sitting on a long term investment in the market can
prove to be very fatal.
Therefore, many people do not understand the meaning of
very small and small investments in good quality stocks.
Its meaning is very simple that you have
hydration. Suppose you want to buy any company,
then do
not make the mistake of buying them at the same time in which market.
Network member buy Renu, then
buy 15000, then share it. If
you do so much of this kind of practice in the market, then
its benefit can prove to be very good for the long term. So, we will
talk about this
trick as well. The performance has been seen to be
very good. If you
talk about one year, then it
turns out to be very good. You are getting returns of around two dozen. So,
you were moving ahead very well with speed,
but after doing which person, there is a
big stop.  To see the decline,
stop much lower. The
support level formed, which means the
portal was created from around 250,
see its stop at Hisar. You
can see it here. Now, apart from this, you
can talk about the performance of the staff speech, although after its listing, the
passbook will be a house. As far as the
long-term chart since its listing is concerned, you can see that the
returns here are approximately
around 22%. Take long-term
interest. And if you are
keeping an eye on the stocks of the life insurance sector, then
look at HDFC Life, this pin should be the
number one choice, its Facebook Lite.
But yes, such punch lines are also very
busy and when we talk about the life
insurance sector, cover this fort. This is going to be
very important, so keep an
eye on it from a trading perspective. If the
results are very good, do not think from a long-term
perspective, but if you have short trouble, you
can try calling. And this is for the
long-term investors, so
see around which level it should point.  375 is also a
bad stop to reach
around 500, so now you are getting such a cheap balance
and how cheap should you be because
it has come up after reaching around 235, so
if someone asks for it in the first few hours then it is a
good thing, but till now no one has taken
advantage of that opportunity, so I would
like to tell them one thing, 350 is a
very good support level for explosive stocks, if the
results of brightness are bad then
that topic will see a decline
due to its stop pressure, there will be some time, we can
definitely see terrorism of 350, then
they can try to enter the Bigg Boss topic, it
looks like a very good level for the last Twenty20 and after that it
creates in the hospital at the same note level,
friends,
how easy is it to wait for a skin around 35, see, there should be a
big decline in its market, by then it can
come back to around 250 only,
possibilities are full because this whole
Mario is going to prove very difficult,
but still, instead of waiting too long, give up